justgottadive.com 2019-05-04

# Privacy | Just Gotta Dive (JGD)

Just Gotta Dive (JGD)  is committing to safeguarding your privacy and our Privacy Policy (“Policy”) explains how we will treat any personal information you supply to us, or that we collect from you on the Just Gotta Dive Website.  Please read this Policy carefully as it affects your legal rights. If you do not agree with this Policy, please do not use the Just Gotta Dive Website.

1.     

INFORMATION COLLECTED   

We may collect information from you when you register on our website, subscribe to our newsletter, or make a purchase.  This information may include your name, contact details, demographics, travel preferences, and billing information.

You may choose not to provide information to us, but we do require certain information in order for you to register as a member, interact in our dive community, book travel, post content to any area of our website, ask a question or provide feedback, or to initiate any other transactions on our website.

2.     

USE OF COOKIES

Cookies are small files that a website or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser should you allow them.  These cookies enable the website and or its service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

The toolbar on most web browsers has a help feature which can provide you with instructions on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies,  have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or disable all cookies.  If you choose to refuse to accept cookies, you may not be able to access certain features and tools offered on our website. 

3.     

USE OF YOUR INFORMATION

We may use any of the information that we collect from you to personalize your experience, notify you of special offers, travel packages, products and services that you may hold your interest , provide you with details on requested products and services, complete a travel booking, enhance our website, improve customer service and support, and send periodic emails. 

4.     

SHARING YOUR INFORMATION

We may disclose your information to any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes defined in this Policy.  In addition, we may disclose information about you: (a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law; (b) in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings; (c) in order to establish, exercise, or defend our legal rights including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk; or (d) to the purchaser or prospective purchaser of any business or asset which we are or are contemplating selling.

5.     

SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION

While no website can guarantee security, we have the necessary security measures in place and will take all reasonable administrative, technical, physical, and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse, or alteration of your personal information.  Only authorized representatives of Just Gotta Dive are permitted to access personal information, and they may only do so for permitted business functions.  Additionally, we use encryption when transmitting your sensitive personal information between your computer and our systems.

6.     

THIRD PARTY LINKS

The Just Gotta Dive Website may include links to third party websites that offer certain  products or services.   These sites do not operate under this Policy and, as a result, we recommend that you examine the privacy statements of these websites to understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information.  Just Gotta Dive (JGD) is not responsible or liable for the content, privacy policies,  or practices of any such websites.  Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these websites.

7.     

SPECIAL PROVISIONS TO USERS OUTSIDE OF THE UNITED STATES

If you are visiting our website from outside of the United States, please be advised that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States.  The data protection laws of the United States may not be as comprehensive as those in your country, but please rest assured that we will always take the necessary steps to ensure that your privacy is protected.  By using our services, you understand and agree that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we may share it with as described in this Policy. 

8.     

CONSENT

You consent to this Policy by using the Just Gotta Dive Website.

9.     

CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

We may make changes to this Policy and, as a result, we recommend that you periodically review it for any updates. 

10.  

CONTACT US

If you have any questions regarding this Policy, please contact us.
